A Guide to the Robert N. Giaimo Papers 1980.0003
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series VII: Project Files, undated, 1962-1980
  - Subseries C: Third District Towns
    - North Branford
      - Open Space (Box 231:, Folder 7732)
      - Police (Box 231:, Folder 7733)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 231:, Folder 7734)
      - Rural Development Act Funding (Box 231:, Folder 7735)
      - Sewer Interceptor (Box 231:, Folder 7736)
    - North Haven
      - Alcohol Education Program (Box 231:, Folder 7737)
      - Algonquin Pipeline (Box 231:, Folder 7738)
      - Banton Street Flood Project (Box 231:, Folder 7739)
      - Beach Street Bridge (Box 231:, Folder 7740)
      - Bicentennial Commission (Box 231:, Folder 7741)
      - Community Service Cadet Officer Program (Box 231:, Folder 7742)
      - Community Services Program (Box 231:, Folder 7743)
      - Education (Box 231:, Folder 7744-7745)
      - Federal Grants (Box 231:, Folder 7746)
      - Flood Plan (Box 231:, Folder 7747)
      - General (Box 231:, Folder 7748)
      - Housing (Box 231:, Folder 7749-7750)
      - Inner City Co-op Form (Box 231:, Folder 7751)
      - Interfaith Housing Elderly Corporation (Box 231:, Folder 7752)
      - Run Away Youth Program (Box 231:, Folder 7753)
      - Sewer Interceptor (Box 231:, Folder 7754)
      - Sewage System (Box 231:, Folder 7755)
      - Sports Arena (Box 231:, Folder 7756)
      - Streets (Box 231:, Folder 7757)
      - Tercentenary Parade (Box 231:, Folder 7758)
      - Water, Sewer (Box 231:, Folder 7759)
    - Orange
      - Bicentennial (Box 231:, Folder 7760)
      - Education (Box 231:, Folder 7761)
      - Federal Grants (Box 231:, Folder 7762)
      - General (Box 231:, Folder 7763)
      - Open Spaces (Box 231:, Folder 7764)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 231:, Folder 7765)
      - Sewer and Water (Box 231:, Folder 7766)
      - Water Pollution (Box 231:, Folder 7767)
    - Stratford (Box not specified)
      - Barnum Festival (Box 232:, Folder 7768)
      - Beach Erosion (Box 232:, Folder 7769)
      - Bicentennial Commission (Box 232:, Folder 7770)
      - Board of Education (Box 232:, Folder 7771)
      - Bruce Brook (Box 232:, Folder 7772)
      - Cultural Commission (Box 232:, Folder 7773)
      - EDA (Box 232:, Folder 7774)
      - Education (Box 232:, Folder 7775)
      - Elderly Housing (Box 232:, Folder 7776-7777)
      - Federal Grants (Box 232:, Folder 7778)
      - Flood, Hurricane and Marshland Problems (Box 232:, Folder 7779)
      - Fresh Pond Urban Renewal (Box 232:, Folder 7780-7781)
      - General (Box 232:, Folder 7782-7783)
      - Government Subsidy (Box 232:, Folder 7784)
      - Greater Bridgeport Regional Solid Waste Commission (Box 232:, Folder 7785)
      - Housatonic River Navigational Improvement (Box 232:, Folder 7786)
      - Housing (Box 232:, Folder 7787-7789)
      - Johnson's Creek and Lewis Cut Dredging (Box 232:, Folder 7790)
      - Judson House (Box 232:, Folder 7791)
      - Lighthouse (Box 232:, Folder 7792)
      - Open Space Project (Box 232:, Folder 7793)
      - Redevelopment (Box 232:, Folder 7794)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 232:, Folder 7795)
      - SBA Flood Disaster Declaration (Box 232:, Folder 7796)
      - Sterling Homestead (Box 232:, Folder 7797)
      - Stratford Youth Corps (Box 232:, Folder 7798)
      - Water and Sewer (Box 232:, Folder 7799)
      - Water Pollution (Box 232:, Folder 7800)
    - Wallingford
      - Bartier House (Box 232:, Folder 7801)
      - Bicentennial Commission (Box 232:, Folder 7802)
      - Block Grants (Box 232:, Folder 7803)
      - Education (Box 232:, Folder 7804)
      - Federal Grants (Box 232:, Folder 7805)
      - General (Box 232:, Folder 7806-7807)
      - Housing (Box 232:, Folder 7808)
      - HUD Discretionary Funds (Box 232:, Folder 7809)
      - Industrial Park (Box 232:, Folder 7810)
      - Meriden-Wallingford Community Mental Health Center (Box 232:, Folder 7811)
      - Meriden-Wallingford Comprehensive Health Planning Agency (Box 232:, Folder 7812)
      - Neighborhood Development Program (Box 232:, Folder 7813)
      - Open Space (Box 232:, Folder 7814)
      - Public Library (Box 232:, Folder 7815)
      - Silver Pond Apartments (Box 232:, Folder 7816)
      - Transportation, Public (Box 232:, Folder 7817)
      - Watershed Program (Box 232:, Folder 7818)
      - Utilities System (Box 232:, Folder 7819)
      - Water and Sewer (Box 232:, Folder 7820)
    - West Haven
      - Adult Day Care (Box 232:, Folder 7821)
      - Bayshore Manor Housing (Box 232:, Folder 7822)
      - Beautification Grant Inquiry (Box 232:, Folder 7823)
      - Bicentennial Commission> (Box 232:, Folder 7824)
      - Cub Scouts (Box 232:, Folder 7825)
      - Demonstration Grant, 1966 (Box 232:, Folder 7826)
      - Education (Box 232:, Folder 7827-7828)
      - Employment (Box 233:, Folder 7829)
      - FCC Application (Box 233:, Folder 7830)
      - Federal Grants (Box 233:, Folder 7831)
      - Flood Insurance (Box 233:, Folder 7832)
      - Forest Road Condos (Box 233:, Folder 7833)
      - General (Box 233:, Folder 7834-7835)
      - High School Band (Box 233:, Folder 7836)
      - House Project (Box 233:, Folder 7837)
      - Kimberly Avenue Bridge (Box 233:, Folder 7838)
      - Low-Rent Housing (Box 233:, Folder 7839-7840)
      - Complaint on Meadowbrook Housing (Box 233:, Folder 7841)
      - Memorial Day Parade (Box 233:, Folder 7842)
      - Morgan Lane Bridge (Box 233:, Folder 7843)
      - Neighborhood Youth Corps (Box 233:, Folder 7844)
      - Police (Box 233:, Folder 7845)
      - Redevelopment (Box 233:, Folder 7846)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 233:, Folder 7847)
      - Sandy Point Project (Box 233:, Folder 7848)
      - Savin Rock (Box 233:, Folder 7849-7852)
      - Senior Citizens Center (Box 233:, Folder 7853)
      - Sewer Project (Box 233:, Folder 7854)
      - Shoreline (Box 233:, Folder 7855)
      - Spring Heights Recreation Area (Box 233:, Folder 7856)
      - Spring Street Bus Line (Box 233:, Folder 7857)
      - SMSA (Box 233:, Folder 7858)
      - School Lunch Probe (Box 233:, Folder 7859)
      - Tri-State EDA Grant Application (Box 233:, Folder 7860)
      - Union School, Elderly Housing (Box 233:, Folder 7861)
      - Urban Development Action Grant (Box 233:, Folder 7862)
      - VA Hospital (Box 233:, Folder 7863-7865)
      - Water and Sewer (Box 233:, Folder 7866)
      - Water Pollution Project (Box 233:, Folder 7867)
    - Woodbridge
      - Bicentennial (Box 233:, Folder 7868)
      - Education (Box 233:, Folder 7869)
      - Flood Insurance (Box 233:, Folder 7870)
      - Open Space (Box 233:, Folder 7871-7872)
    - General
      - Census (Box 233:, Folder 7873)
      - Chamber of Commerce (Box 233:, Folder 7874)
      - Connecticut Education Grants (Box 233:, Folder 7875)
      - Consortium for Youth for South Central (Box 233:, Folder 7876)
      - Data (Box 233:, Folder 7877)
      - General (Box 233:, Folder 7878)
      - Historic Places (Box 233:, Folder 7879)
      - HUD Survey Team (Box 233:, Folder 7880)
      - Nike Site (Box 233:, Folder 7881-7882)
      - Poverty Program (Box 233:, Folder 7883)
      - Public Works (Box 233a:, Folder 7884-7887)
      - Revenue Sharing (Box 233a:, Folder 7888)
      - SBA Loans (Box 233a:, Folder 7889)
      - SMSA Data (Box 233a:, Folder 7890-7891)
      - State Payments to Medical Vendors (Box 233a:, Folder 7892)
      - Unemployment and Income Statistics (Box 233a:, Folder 7893)
      - Veteran's Counseling Center (Box 233a:, Folder 7894)
  - Subseries D: Case Files
    - A.C. Gilbert Tariffs on Toys (Box 234:, Folder 7895-7896)
    - Accelerated Electron, Inc. (Government Contract) (Box 234:, Folder 7897)
    - Acme Music Corp. (Box 234:, Folder 7898)
    - Advance Development Corp. (Box 234:, Folder 7899)
    - Afro House (Box 234:, Folder 7900)
    - Agriculture Stabilization and Conservation Offices Closing (Box 234:, Folder 7901)
    - Agriculture Company of Pan America (Box 234:, Folder 7902)
    - Air Star Routes (Box 234:, Folder 7903)
    - Aircraft Radio Industries, Inc. (Box 234:, Folder 7904-7905)
    - Aitro, Imported Italian Cheese (Box 234:, Folder 7906)
    - Algonquin Pipeline (North Haven and Guilford) (Box 234:, Folder 7907-7908)
    - American Acrylics and Plastics (Box 234:, Folder 7909)
    - American Bar Association (Box 234:, Folder 7909)
    - American Cynamid Association (Box 234:, Folder 7910)
    - American Diversified Securities, Inc. (Box 234:, Folder 7911)
    - American Supply Company, Air Force (Box 234:, Folder 7912)
    - American Refractories and Crucible Corporation (Box 234:, Folder 7913)
    - Amity High School Lunch Program (Anderson, Edna) (Box 234:, Folder 7914)
    - Amputee Center (Box 234:, Folder 7915)
    - AMSA/AEC Employees, Department of the Army (Box 234:, Folder 7916)
    - Ardon House Conference (Box 234:, Folder 7917)
    - Are Cooperative Education Services (Box 234:, Folder 7918)
    - Armstrong Rubber (Box 234:, Folder 7919-7921)
    - Arnold Foundry (Box 234:, Folder 7922-7923)
    - Arthritis Foundation, Connecticut (Box 234:, Folder 7924)
    - Atkinson Construction Company (Box 234:, Folder 7925)
    - Atlantic Sales Agency (Box 234:, Folder 7926)
    - Atlantic Wire Company (Box 234:, Folder 7927-7928)
    - Auburn Building Maintenance (Box 234:, Folder 7929)
    - Auco Corporation (Box 234:, Folder 7930-7931)
    - BAHA'IS (Iran) (Box 234:, Folder 7932)
    - Bailey, Dr. Joyce W. (Box 234:, Folder 7933)
    - Bailey Junior High School Rocket Club (Box 234:, Folder 7934)
    - Ball and Socket Manufacturing Company (Government Contract) (Box 234:, Folder 7935)
    - Banner Fabrications, Inc. (Box 234:, Folder 7936)
    - Bello I.D. Systems, Inc. (Box 234:, Folder 7937)
    - Benedict and Company (Box 234:, Folder 7938)
    - Benhaven School (Box 234:, Folder 7939)
    - Bic Pen (Box 234:, Folder 7940)
    - Birches of Foxon Condominium Association (Box 234:, Folder 7941)
    - Bisaillon Association (Box 234:, Folder 7942)
    - Blake, Whitney (Box 234:, Folder 7943)
    - Blakeslee Transportation (Box 234:, Folder 7944)
    - Blakeslee Mansion (Box 234:, Folder 7945)
    - Blue Ribbon Food./G.&G. Packing Company (Box 234:, Folder 7946)
    - Boys Club, see Testimonial Dinner (Box 234:, Folder 7947)
    - Bradley's Express (ICC) (Box 234:, Folder 7948)
    - Bradley (Box 234:, Folder 7949)
    - Branford Beach Erosion (Box 234:, Folder 7950)
    - Branford Engineering (Box 234:, Folder 7951)
    - Branford Sewage Treatment Plant (Box 234:, Folder 7982)
    - Bridgeport Leather Specialty Company (Box 234:, Folder 7983)
    - Brown Bolty Advertising (Box 234:, Folder 7984)
    - Brown and Thomas Company (Pension Fund) (Box 234:, Folder 7985)
    - Burk Industries Inc. (Patent Office) (Box 234:, Folder 7986)
    - Business Ventures (Box 234:, Folder 7987)
    - Cohn Engineers (Box 234:, Folder 7988-7989)
    - CBC Construction Company (Box 234:, Folder 7990)
    - Coplan & Sons Electrical Contractors (Box 234:, Folder 7991)
    - Cappas, Emmanuel (Box 234:, Folder 7992)
    - Carafa Construction (Box 234:, Folder 7993)
    - CCIA Investigation (Box 235:, Folder 7994-7995)
    - Census Materials (Box 235:, Folder 7996-8004)
    - Central Connecticut Communications (FCC License) (Box 235:, Folder 8005)
    - Century Brass (Box 235:, Folder 8006)
    - Cerro Wire Company (Box 235:, Folder 8007-8008)
    - Char-Len Handbags, Inc. (Box 235:, Folder 8009)
    - Chesire Products (Box 235:, Folder 8010)
    - Chesire Public Library (Box 235:, Folder 8011)
    - Children's Foundation (Box 235:, Folder 8012)
    - Children's House (Box 235:, Folder 8013)
    - Children's T.V. Theater (Box 235:, Folder 8014)
    - City Wide Neighborhood (HEW Grants) (Box 235:, Folder 8015)
    - Chlorine, New Haven (Box 235:, Folder 8016)
    - Clifford Beers Guidance Clinic (Federal Funds) (Box 235:, Folder 8017-8018)
    - Clinical Analysis Service (Box 235:, Folder 8019)
    - Club Thirty, Inc. (Box 235:, Folder 8020)
    - Cody Power Equipment (Box 235:, Folder 8021)
    - Coast Guard Boating Safety (Box 235:, Folder 8022)
    - Cognitronics Corporation (Box 235:, Folder 8023)
    - Collins First Aid (Box 235:, Folder 8024)
    - Colt Plant in South Korea (Box 235:, Folder 8025)
    - Columbia Towers (Box 235:, Folder 8026)
    - Combustion Efficiency Corporation (Box 235:, Folder 8027)
    - Community Housing, Inc. (Box 235:, Folder 8028)
    - Congress Pants Store (Box 235:, Folder 8029)
    - Connecticut
      - Agriculture Export Station (Commemorative Stamp) (Box 235:, Folder 8030)
      - Capitol Region Child Care Center (Box 235:, Folder 8031)
      - Cartridge (Box 235:, Folder 8032)
      - Child Welfare Association (Box 235:, Folder 8033)
      - Connecticut Company (Box 235:, Folder 8034)
      - Educational T.V. (Box 235:, Folder 8035)
      - Hospital Association Grant (Box 235:, Folder 8036)
      - Hospital Equipment Company (Box 235:, Folder 8037)
      - Ice Yacht Club (Box 235:, Folder 8038)
      - Light and Power Company (Box 235:, Folder 8039)
      - Medical Society (Box 235:, Folder 8040)
      - Motor Lines, Inc. (Box 235:, Folder 8041)
      - Petroleum Association (Box 235:, Folder 8042)
      - CPTV Application (Box 235:, Folder 8043)
      - Research Center (Box 235:, Folder 8044)
      - Reserve Supply Company (Box 235:, Folder 8045)
      - Salute to Space (Box 235:, Folder 8046)
      - Scientific Center (Box 235:, Folder 8047)
      - Sign Association (Box 235:, Folder 8048)
      - State Employees Association (Box 235:, Folder 8049)
      - Telephone and Electric of Meriden (Box 235:, Folder 8050)
      - Two-Way Radio Company (Box 235:, Folder 8051)
      - Union of Telephone Workers (Box 235:, Folder 8052)
      - Women's Educational and Legal Fund (Box 235:, Folder 8053)
    - Contract Hardware, Inc. (Box 235:, Folder 8054)
    - Crown Towers Apartments (Box 235:, Folder 8055)
    - Currier Machine Sales (Box 235:, Folder 8056)
    - Curtis Machine Sales (Box 235:, Folder 8057)
    - Danbury Prison Fire (Box 235:, Folder 8058)
    - Dream Lake Development (Box 235:, Folder 8059)
    - East Shore Senior Citizens (Box 235:, Folder 8060)
    - Easter Seals Goodwill Industry, see New Haven Area Rehabilitation Center (Box 236:, Folder 8061)
    - Echlin-Berg (Trailer Brakes) (Box 236:, Folder 8062)
    - Employment, City of Milford (Box 236:, Folder 8063)
    - Farnum Neighborhood House (Box 236:, Folder 8064)
    - Fairfield County Veterans' Memorial Association (Box 236:, Folder 8065)
    - Family Practice Residencies Applications (Hospital of St. Raphael) (Box 236:, Folder 8066)
    - Ferris Engine Company (Hydraulic Engine) (Box 236:, Folder 8067)
    - Foot Guard Commemorative Stamp (Box 236:, Folder 8068)
    - Foremost Foods Company (Box 236:, Folder 8069)
    - Fort Nathan Hale Park (Box 236:, Folder 8070)
    - Forty-Third Division (Box 236:, Folder 8071)
    - Gaylord Hospital (Box 236:, Folder 8072)
    - General Star Products (Box 236:, Folder 8073)
    - Guilford School (Box 236:, Folder 8074)
    - Global Building Maintenance (Box 236:, Folder 8075)
    - Glazers and Glassworkers (Box 236:, Folder 8076)
    - Goodpseed Opera House Foundation (Box 236:, Folder 8077)
    - Goodwill Industries of Central Connecticut (Box 236:, Folder 8078)
    - Governor's Foot Guard (Europe Trip) (Box 236:, Folder 8079)
    - Grace New Hampshire Hospital (Box 236:, Folder 8080)
    - Graphic Designs Group (Box 236:, Folder 8081)
    - Graphic Film (Box 236:, Folder 8082)
    - Greater New Haven Business Development Corporation (Box 236:, Folder 8083)
    - Hamden Forest, Insect and Disease Lab (Box 236:, Folder 8084)
    - Harsay Immigration (Box 236:, Folder 8085)
    - Hatry Electronics Enterprises, Inc. (Box 236:, Folder 8086)
    - Hebrew Day School (New Haven) (Box 236:, Folder 8087)
    - Heritage Trail Markers (Box 236:, Folder 8088)
    - Hartford Foster Grandparents Day (Box 236:, Folder 8089)
    - High Standards Manufacturing Company (Box 236:, Folder 8090)
    - H.N. Industries (Box 236:, Folder 8091)
    - Hoggson and Pettis Manufacturing Company (Box 236:, Folder 8092)
    - Home Health Care of Connecticut (Box 236:, Folder 8093)
    - Home Maintenance Corporation (Box 236:, Folder 8094)
    - Housing and Urban Development Investigations
      - Meadowbrook Apartments (Box 236:, Folder 8095)
      - Redevelopment Agency (Box 236:, Folder 8096)
      - Housing Authority (Box 236:, Folder 8097)
    - Housing Guidance Council (Box 236:, Folder 8098)
    - Hull Dye and Print Works, Inc. (Box 236:, Folder 8099)
    - Indian Point Club Association, Ltd. (Box 236:, Folder 8100)
    - Industrial Conference (Box 236:, Folder 8101)
    - Information and Counseling Service for Women (Box 236:, Folder 8102)
    - Institute Publishing Company (Box 236:, Folder 8103)
    - Insurance Association of Connecticut (Box 236:, Folder 8104)
    - International Silver Company (Box 236:, Folder 8105)
    - Intercoastal Shipping Services (Box 236:, Folder 8106)
    - Italian American Civil Rights League (Box 236:, Folder 8107)
    - Italian American Foundation (Box 236:, Folder 8108)
    - Italian Relief Commission (Box 237:, Folder 8109)
    - Ives, HB and Company (Box 237:, Folder 8110)
    - Jackson Iron and Steel Company (Box 237:, Folder 8111)
    - Jeho O. Smith Community Youth Center (Box 237:, Folder 8112)
    - JET Program (Box 237:, Folder 8113)
    - Jewish Home for the Aged (Ginsberg, Gary) (Box 237:, Folder 8114)
    - John Magee House, Inc. (LEAA Funds) (Box 237:, Folder 8115)
    - JFK Library for Minorities (Box 237:, Folder 8116)
    - Kaufman, Jordan (Guilford Pharmacy) (Box 237:, Folder 8117)
    - Kennedy, Medi-Care, Title XIX (Box 237:, Folder 8118)
    - Kreiger Welding Fabrication (Box 237:, Folder 8119)
    - Laduby Company (Flur-o-lack) (Box 237:, Folder 8120)
    - Laurel Heights Hospital (Box 237:, Folder 8121)
    - Lawrence Transport, Inc. (Army) (Box 237:, Folder 8122)
    - Lenart Trucking Company (Box 237:, Folder 8123)
    - Life Enrichment Activity Program (Box 237:, Folder 8124)
    - Little Sisters of the Poor (Box 237:, Folder 8125)
    - Live Structures Inc. (Stratford) (Box 237:, Folder 8126)
    - Lucson Industrial Corporation (Edward Richo) (Box 237:, Folder 8127)
    - Machinery Auctioneering Company (Box 237:, Folder 8128)
    - Madison Historical Society (Box 237:, Folder 8129)
    - Mallard Manufacturing Company (Box 237:, Folder 8130)
    - Manpower Inc. (Navy Contract) (Box 237:, Folder 8131)
    - Manufacturing Association of Bridgeport (Box 237:, Folder 8132)
    - Martin, WR (Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen) (Box 237:, Folder 8133)
    - Mathewson Tool Company (Box 237:, Folder 8134)
    - May, Jonathan (Box 237:, Folder 8135)
    - Media Associates (Box 237:, Folder 8136)
    - Merit Food Services (Box 237:, Folder 8137)
    - Meriden A-6 (Highways) (Box 237:, Folder 8138)
    - Merit Coal and Energy Company (Box 237:, Folder 8139)
    - Meriden Flood Control Program (Box 237:, Folder 8140)
    - Meriden Highway (Box 237:, Folder 8141)
    - Meriden Public Works (Box 237:, Folder 8142)
    - Meriden Redevelopment (Box 237:, Folder 8143)
    - Meriden-Wallingford SMSA Case (Box 237:, Folder 8144)
    - Meyer Laboratories (Box 237:, Folder 8145)
    - Meyer, Mrs. W.H. (White House) (Box 237:, Folder 8146)
    - Metro Life Insurance Company (Anti-Trust Prosecution) (Box 237:, Folder 8147)
    - Microban (Box 237:, Folder 8148)
    - Middletown Canal Operation (Box 237:, Folder 8149)
    - MIF Industries (Box 237:, Folder 8150)
    - Mildin Institute (Box 237:, Folder 8151)
    - Milford Armory (Box 237:, Folder 8152)
    - Milford Automatics (Box 237:, Folder 8153)
    - Milford Creative Guidance, Inc. (Box 237:, Folder 8154)
    - Milford Elementary School Russian Trip (Box 237:, Folder 8155)
    - Milford Memorial Parade and Request (Box 237:, Folder 8156)
    - Milford Redevelopment (Box 237:, Folder 8157)
    - Mite Corporation (Box 237:, Folder 8158-8159)
    - Mizrachi Women's Organization of American Aid (Grant Application) (Box 237:, Folder 8160)
    - Mocatta Metals Corporation (Box 237:, Folder 8161)
    - Modern Air Decor (Box 237:, Folder 8162)
    - Moon, Stephen (Box 237:, Folder 8163)
    - Mossberg Gun Manufacturing Company (Box 237:, Folder 8164-8165)
    - MS Equipment Company (Military) (Box 237:, Folder 8166)
    - Mt. Olive African Methodist Episcopal Zion Church (Box 237:, Folder 8167)
    - Narco, Inc. (Box 237:, Folder 8168)
    - NASA Recruitment (Box 237:, Folder 8169)
    - NASA Center (Box 237:, Folder 8170)
    - National Association of Theater Owners (Robert Spodick, The Price Commission) (Box 237:, Folder 8171)
    - National Defender Institute (Grant Application) (Box 237:, Folder 8172)
    - National Folding Box (Box 237:, Folder 8173)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 237:, Folder 8174)
    - New England Farm Workers Council (Bruce Y. Candelaria) (Box 237:, Folder 8175)
    - New England Motor Rates (Box 237:, Folder 8176)
    - New England Pipe Cleaning Service (Box 238:, Folder 8177)
    - New England Tree Expert Company (Box 238:, Folder 8178)
    - New England Regional Center (Box 238:, Folder 8179)
    - New England Farm Workers Council (Box 238:, Folder 8180)
    - Nellis Air Force Base (Box 238:, Folder 8181)
    - Newhallville Youth Association (Box 238:, Folder 8182)
    - New Haven ABCD (Box 238:, Folder 8183)
    - New Haven Airways/Ransome Jet Fuel (Box 238:, Folder 8184-8187)
    - New Haven Area Rehabilitation Center (Easter Seal Goodwill Industries) (Box 238:, Folder 8188-8205)
    - New Haven Association for Retarded Children (Box 238:, Folder 8206)
    - New Haven Children's Museum (Box 238:, Folder 8207)
    - New Haven Halfway House (Box 238:, Folder 8208)
    - New Haven VA Hospital (Box 238:, Folder 8209)
    - New Haven Volunteers (ACTION Grant Application) (Box 238:, Folder 8210)
    - New Samaritan Group (Box 238:, Folder 8211)
    - Norris Machine and Tool Company (Box 238:, Folder 8212)
    - North Vietnam Medical Supplies (Box 238:, Folder 8213)
    - Novaro and Company (Box 238:, Folder 8214)
    - O'Sullivan Fuel Company (Defense Contract) (Box 238:, Folder 8215)
    - Parochial Advisory Committee (Box 238:, Folder 8216)
    - Pinecrest Subdivision (Box 238:, Folder 8217)
    - Planned Parenthood League (HEW Grant) (Box 238:, Folder 8218)
    - Political Appointments (Employment/Unemployment) (Box 238:, Folder 8219)
    - Pond Lily Company (Box 238:, Folder 8220)
    - Project Seek-Out (Box 239:, Folder 8221-8222)
    - Quinnipiac Council (BSA) (Box 239:, Folder 8223)
    - Robert Thompson (Environment, Inc.) (Box 239:, Folder 8224)
    - Roger Sherman School (Box 239:, Folder 8225-8226)
    - SAAB (New Haven Terminal) (Box 239:, Folder 8227)
    - Saarinen Associated (Box 239:, Folder 8228)
    - Sacred Heart Church (Box 239:, Folder 8229)
    - Savin Bay Nursing Home (HUD Conditional Commitment) (Box 239:, Folder 8230)
    - Sea and Air Products (Box 239:, Folder 8231)
    - Shakespeare Summer Festival, D.C. (Box 239:, Folder 8232)
    - Shubert Theatre Folder (Box 239:, Folder 8233)
    - Sister Kenny Institute (Abbott-Northwestern Hospital) (Box 239:, Folder 8234)
    - Southwater Corporation (Box 239:, Folder 8235)
    - Spanish Cultural Association (Box 239:, Folder 8236)
    - Spina-Bifida Clinic (New Haven) (Box 239:, Folder 8237)
    - St. Barbara's Greek Orthodox (Box 239:, Folder 8238)
    - St. Peter's School (NDEA Case) (Box 239:, Folder 8239)
    - St. Rapael's Hospital (Box 239:, Folder 8240-8244)
    - Testimonial Dinner, New Haven Boys Club (Box 239:, Folder 8245-8248)
    - Student Learning Center (Box 239:, Folder 8249)
    - Sunworks (Box 239:, Folder 8250)